[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
thanks for Lending me some help buddy
usually I would pay you with a case of
beer and some Twizzlers but I think they
got entangled in my hairy ass crack when
I sat on them to put on my socks haha
so are you coming to the big party this
afternoon with your family it would mean
the world to us if you do it
I said no
so anyway me and two guys are throwing
it later in Home Depot
Todd lost the ability to walk in the war
and I want to cheer them up
and his brother I met in Home Depot we
put all of our money together and we
have enough to afford to hold fireworks
well
is no
okay yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so I've been meaning to ask how are
things going with what you and Knuckles
obviously rumor has it around school you
finally ask him out
well there's going to be a party later
at Home Depot so we were planning on
hanging out there I might call it autho
who has a date at Home Depot
no way no way you deserve it maybe I
could even help you do your hair before
you go oh thanks for a little tour my
own personal Matchmaker
I'm glad at least one person is out
there looking out for me
your own personal angel I won't even
charge you
[Music]
[Applause]
knock knock girls I brought snacks
manikai said no throwing your dried out
poop balls in the house
you better shut up before I smack you
that's it young man go to your room
Little Debbie Oatmeal cream pies oh miss
Hedgehog this is too much I haven't even
the faintest clue as to why you're being
so nice to me
that's because a good girl like yourself
doesn't come around often no go on eat
all the oatmeal cream pies you want
don't worry if you get tired you can
just use the spare room at the end of
the hall to stay the night
well sirs this is the Most Blessed I've
felt all month thank you Alina people
are usually so complicated but you make
it so easy to not feel hated
I'll remember your kind words tonight
when I say my evening prayers
oh yeah Sonia I need you to do something
for me Ya Mama take these firecrackers
and put them in the car but don't let
Uncle Chuck see how cheap they are or he
might come and beat me up okay
haha this is so fun what should we blow
up next how about my Uncle Chuck's Jesus
action figure that thing's been a thorn
in my ass for far too long
sounds good prep the bad boy
laughs
oh God the missile is on fire manic poop
on him before the fire spreads
[Music]
dang boy I said poop not gas him up
that's all I got I didn't have breakfast
yet you have to use your people I've
been waiting for this
this is boring let's head downstairs and
see if your mom has any snacks
no way you got jalapeno Cheeto flavored
mac and cheese
manic you've been holding out on me all
this time big deal our mom finds it in
the clearance section at Walmart every
week
you don't get it this isn't your typical
mac and cheese this is super Advanced
mac and cheese we have to break open a
box tonight when everyone else is
shooting fireworks at the Home Depot
we'll be the ones having a real party in
the back
you know what [__] it go get a saucepan
I'll hide it in my butthole
Sonia we need to have a talk
again it was maniku stole your
underpants I don't wear underwear [__]
not that when were you going to tell me
you and Knuckles started dating
I am so sick of you thinking you have
the right to make your own choices in
life
are you saying I don't
um obviously girls are dumb when are you
going to realize that Knuckles is an
[__] he steals from us every chance
he gets and he beats you up all the time
not true Knuckles is a cutie pie
[Music]
evidence eased without a warrant candy
tossed out in the court of law
listen to me sis first time you guys
hang out you're going to end up in a
fight and to fist up your ass next
you'll be bitching school with him and
manic oh now the truth comes out you're
not worried about me at all you're only
jealous because I would rather hang out
with him instead of you
when are you going to quit being such a
narcissistic little [__] I am not a
narcissist what about when you named our
band that wasn't me
[Music]
foreign
you know before we write our music we
have to come up with a catchy band name
first
say what about hedgehogs of the
Underground
pretty cool sis how about the tryhogs as
in Triangle since there's three of us
how about Sonic Underground because
that's what I want to call it bitters
or how about we we are not going to
debate this
we could always try it we're done
you know what both of you go to bed this
pizza is mine too
[Music]
evidence seized without a warrant can be
tossed out in the court of law Richard
oh you just don't get it me and manic
have always lived in your Shadow and it
was easy for us to stay there because
you are so fat there was always plenty
of room but time changes people now come
on we have a party at Home Depot to get
to that is if you still love America
[Music]
look at it they face ain't she a beauty
it sure is my only friend after a lot of
years we finally got enough money by
working at Carlos O'Kelly's to buy a car
of our very own we never could have
achieved this with the pay Robotnik was
given us
hahaha
Mexico sleet look it's our old boss and
friend Dr Robotnik and he's in one of
those Mexican bouncing cars with some
lovely ladies oh I'm so happy for him
aren't you asleep it's so nice how we
are all doing well in our own right
well well well how do you do ladies
they're Robotnik nice pick code it looks
like Jared Leto where did you get it
also can you turn the Mexican music down
a bit no and thanks I was able to
purchase it with a leftover paychecks I
was going to give you the day you quit
did you know I was actually going to
give you a raise that day
how unfortunate that you decided to
leave when you did
ma what a funny string of circumstances
that lead to this that it's okay sleep
and I don't need money nor [__] to be
happy because we have each other sleep
just got off work he cleans tables at
the local Carlos O'Kelly's now he always
cries into the bathroom after work but
we make do it doesn't even matter that
we're sixteen thousand dollars in debt
because I spend all of our money on
OverWatch 2 skins
Ling face this is not what we rehearsed
I'm not going to lie for you fool
[Music]
well I shouldn't keep the girls waiting
they love me because I have a stacked
wallet and even more stack balls maybe
we'll meet up again in the future in
this ocean we call life
[Music]
oh and sleet I went to Carlos O'Kelly's
at noon and accidentally pooped on a
chair when I thought it was going to be
a fart
I was too embarrassed to tell anybody so
make sure you get to it although it's
probably seeped into the cushions by now
so it'll be a lot of work
isn't it funny how you don't work for me
and yet you still have to clean my poop
[Laughter]
come on Cyrus throw me a fast one really
make it count I want to grab your balls
oh man you're really good but I'm better
good job batting today Trevor you were
able to make the ball go more than three
feet this time
maybe in 28 years you'll be able to play
baseball as good as a 12 year old
well I can't take all the credit after
all you're the one who taught me how to
aim for balls
what does that mean
simply put it means you have nice balls
okay but maybe you shouldn't talk about
balls at a preschool baseball field
well they don't have to be here
Trevor we climbed over the fence we are
literally in a preschool
they're babies where could they go
good job today Trevor you're really good
with balls
I was going to present you with this
prize that I was hiding between my fire
and balls if you were able to hit a ball
over the fence but who did so bad that I
feel sorry for you so I'm going to give
it to you anyway yummy is that a
chocolate chip cookie pizza
that is right I had intended to give it
to my beach but I can't be in touch with
him for a few hours for use I just
closed a deal alongside ninja from
twitch to purchase 29 countries now some
assassins are coming after us and he
wants me to hide him in a helicopter so
they can't find his s
oh look at the time ideally must be off
if you see my beach do give him my
regards
ninja maybe you could show me some of
those silly Fortnight dancers haha
especially the one the two did at the
New Year's party
okay
see yet wouldn't one of the yard
features
check it out there's so many people at
the party already this is gonna be off
the hook
yo [__] you got my Happy Meal munchies
right here darling a Whopper from Burger
King and root beer with crushed ice your
favorite Burger King guess you [__] up
because I asked from McDonald's
specifically a quarter pounder with
cheese with french fries and a Grimace
Shake now it is my manly obligation to
put you in your plate
you know Knox we may disagree on a lot
of things but if there's one thing we
can agree on it's that boy's Rule and
girls drool
leave it to Home Depot to bring the boys
together come on boys let's go eat some
macaroni
thanks again for helping me do this Miss
dollar tour
Todd has been really depressed since
coming home from war
especially since he's in a wheelchair
now which causes people to bully him
don't sweat the bill I would have thrown
a party regardless because I think Wars
are cool that's why George Bush is my
favorite President because he did 911 so
we can go to war instead of sit on our
butts
so Bob Bill tells me you're a huge fan
of the NASCAR driver Tony Stewart
so am I wasn't it really cool when he
ran over some guy and killed him
a man of few words I like that
real men like a slit our actions do the
talking and from all that I've heard you
are one of the kindest and sweetest men
I know
excuse me do you guys need help finding
anything
no we are just rowing a Fourth of July
party
while I'm afraid you're going to have to
wrap up this little bash [__] because
it's way past the 4th of July and you're
blocking the aisle for my fat [__]
ass my boss just told me some kids are
eating mac and cheese somewhere and I
have to find them before I get fired and
before you say it I know I'm sexy not I
can't go five minutes without someone
complimenting on my fat ass
listen here bucko I'm doing this for a
friend
friend I don't see [__] [__]
hey where did my friend go
got to say boys I thought you were
pooping on my butt but you really pulled
through with this one the Mac really
does taste like Cheetos
hey there pal you looking for some grub
there's plenty here
manic don't be a stupid that guy is in a
wheelchair which means he is weird and
different do your due diligence and
ignore him until he leaves
oh
[Music]
my God that bastard wasn't crippled at
all he's been lying to us this whole
time
are we just going to sit here and do
nothing put a fire under it lads
[Applause]
[Music]
for me
Todd what has happened
a couple of teenagers suddenly my
wheelchair go start the car I'll get the
fireworks
already damn it Todd this is worse than
when we hacked into a guy's game of
Minecraft and pretended to be zombies to
steal diamonds from his in-game world
thought you could walk Say It Isn't So I
threw you a party and everything I
should have known you weren't really a
Make-a-Wish kid because you're 37 years
old
why did you do it
why because I want to be the center of
attention all people seem to care about
these days of the TV show Sonic
Underground but what about me what about
Tom I work an eight-hour job every day
but nobody wants to talk about me and I
am sick of it so even me if I can make
many little towers [__] dad make me a
hot dog in Home Depot it would prove
that he is my [__]
I am not your [__] Todd do you know why
because I'm still having fun no you're
lying I know what you're trying to do
you're trying to make me mad
and if I get angry then you win
but I won't play your little game Dot
whether you like it or not we are still
in the best place any man could dream of
being on a Tuesday in the afternoon in a
random I love a Home Depot
Mindy's dad is right you thought you
could play us but instead all you did
was bring us all together and now we're
going to light some fireworks and party
because that's what the Sonic
Underground does
big deal I saw them all you only have
two Nestle fireworks how can you have
fun with only that
well that's all for today you sexy
fortnite baby boys tune in next time
where I break into the town Dater
ah
ninja from twitch.com are you hurt take
a wild guess Blondie I'm just surprised
it missed my S my beauty takes up over
50 percent of my body weight
yeah and I really thought the Assassins
wouldn't be able to find us I thought we
could walk around unnoticed but I guess
maybe it's because we look like blue and
yellow crayons
troll ninja crawl do it like how they do
in fortnite
everyone get out of my way I'll take it
from here on out
foreign
[Music]
ah
come on
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
thanks again for just starring on my
stream tonight I never had this many
viewers on Twitch at one time before can
you leave now though you're going to
steals my fans away in that case why
don't we finish things off with a bang
[Music]
thank you
well that's all to other fireworks time
to pack it up [__]
every one of someone else is shooting
off fireworks
foreign
[Music]
thank you
why are they turning all of my heroes
into Fair bits
[Music]
everything is fixed all because some
fireworks what a load of [__]
and there you see why every country
since the birth of mankind put stricter
limitations on woman than man because
all they do is [__]
[Music]
lady liberties someday
literally rocks
foreign